Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
President Wen
الرئيس ون
The thing you requested has been delivered.
تم تسليم الشيء الذي طلبته.
I need an explanation.
أحتاج إلى تفسير.
I
أنا
went out to use the restroom.
خرجت لاستخدام دورة المياه.
Then I ran into an acquaintance.
ثم صادفت أحد معارفي.
Talk about a coincidence, right?
يا لها من مصادفة، أليس كذلك؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
It's
إنه
Qian Kexin's family
عائلة تشيان كيكسين
set her up on another blind date.
رتب لها موعداً غرامياً آخر.
Haven't you noticed?
ألم تلاحظ ذلك؟
This whole area is crawling with love surveillance agents.
هذه المنطقة بأكملها تعج بوكلاء مراقبة الحب.
Where?
أين؟
What would you two like to eat?
ماذا ترغبان في تناوله؟
Just a couple of vegetable dishes is fine.
يكفي تقديم طبقين من الخضار.
Then I'll order a few things for you.
سأطلب لك بعض الأشياء بعد ذلك.
Sure, sure, sure.
بالتأكيد، بالتأكيد، بالتأكيد.
I'm really sorry.
أنا آسف حقاً.
It was a momentary lapse on my part.
كان ذلك زلة عابرة من جانبي.
How do we handle this?
كيف نتعامل مع هذا؟
It's all fake anyway.
كل هذا مزيف على أي حال.
Right?
يمين؟
And you?
وأنت؟
Don't care.
لا أهتم.
He doesn't care either.
وهو لا يكترث أيضاً.
What will outsiders think of me?
ماذا سيظن بي الغرباء؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
With my charm,
بفضل سحري،
my woman
امرأتي
would never date another man behind my back.
لن أواعد رجلاً آخر أبداً من وراء ظهري.
That's the point you're concerned about?
هل هذه هي النقطة التي تقلقك؟
Fine, fine, fine.
حسناً، حسناً، حسناً.
You're the client.
أنت العميل.
You call the shots.
أنت صاحب القرار.
I'm starting to wonder if
بدأت أتساءل عما إذا
Hou Yi missed shooting down one sun,
أخطأ هو يي في إسقاط أحد الشموس،
making you shine so brilliantly now.
مما يجعلك تتألقين بشكل رائع الآن.
You're very close to losing control like this.
أنت على وشك فقدان السيطرة على نفسك بهذه الطريقة.
I, Wen Pei'an,
أنا، وين بي آن،
never do anything outside my control.
لن أفعل أي شيء خارج عن سيطرتي.
Okay.
تمام.
One minute.
دقيقة واحدة.
Give me one minute, I'll handle it.
أعطني دقيقة واحدة، وسأتولى الأمر.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Who is that?
من ذاك؟
Him?
له؟
He's my
هو لي
best guy friend.
أفضل صديق لي.
You know?
أنت تعرف؟
So, meeting you for the first time,
لذا، عند لقائنا لأول مرة،
he gets a bit nervous.
يشعر ببعض التوتر.
You could think of it as social phobia.
يمكنك اعتبار ذلك رهابًا اجتماعيًا.
That's why he seems
ولهذا السبب يبدو
a little tense.
متوتر قليلاً.
He does seem quite tense.
يبدو عليه التوتر الشديد.
Let me tell you a secret.
دعني أخبرك سراً.
He just went through a bad breakup.
لقد مرّ للتو بانفصال مؤلم.
It was really tragic.
لقد كان الأمر مأساوياً حقاً.
So he follows me everywhere.
لذا فهو يتبعني في كل مكان.
I'm just worried he might do something rash.
أنا قلقة فقط من أنه قد يفعل شيئاً متهوراً.
So, Senior, how about today we just pretend
إذن، يا أستاذ، ما رأيك أن نتظاهر اليوم فقط؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
I understand completely.
أفهم تماماً.
It's just an extra set of chopsticks, right?
إنها مجرد مجموعة إضافية من عيدان الطعام، أليس كذلك؟
Darn it.
يا إلهي.
The other man is approaching the young master.
الرجل الآخر يقترب من السيد الشاب.
That's not what I meant.
لم أقصد ذلك.
Chairman.
رئيس مجلس الإدارة.
Should we go help?
هل يجب أن نذهب للمساعدة؟
No.
لا.
This sort of thing,
هذا النوع من الأشياء،
let him handle it himself.
دعه يتولى الأمر بنفسه.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Xin Tong told me about your relationship.
أخبرني شين تونغ عن علاقتكما.
You know already?
هل تعلم ذلك بالفعل؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I'm very sorry
أنا آسف جداً
for interrupting your date.
لمقاطعتك لموعدك.
If you don't mind,
إن لم يكن لديك مانع،
we could have dinner together.
يمكننا تناول العشاء معاً.
I think
أظن
that won't be necessary.
لن يكون ذلك ضرورياً.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
As expected of the young master.
كما هو متوقع من السيد الشاب.
His composure is impressive.
رباطة جأشه مثيرة للإعجاب.
He's actually sitting
إنه جالس بالفعل
harmoniously with the other man.
بانسجام مع الرجل الآخر.
Lin Xiang.
لين شيانغ.
Xin Tong and I are former schoolmates.
أنا وشين تونغ زميلان سابقان في المدرسة.
How should I address you?
كيف ينبغي أن أخاطبك؟
A Wen.
أ. وين.
You can call him A Wen.
يمكنك أن تناديه آ وين.
Here.
هنا.
Sweetheart,
حبيب،
your favorite little cake.
كعكتك الصغيرة المفضلة.
The young master is asserting his dominance over the other man.
الشاب السيد يؤكد سيطرته على الرجل الآخر.
This is so delicious.
هذا لذيذ جداً.
Actually, I really envy you.
في الحقيقة، أنا أغبطك بشدة.
It's just that...
الأمر فقط هو...
You don't have to care about worldly opinions.
ليس عليك أن تهتم بآراء العالم.
You can live life according to your own ideas.
يمكنك أن تعيش حياتك وفقًا لأفكارك الخاصة.
Xin Tong has told you quite a bit.
لقد أخبرك شين تونغ بالكثير.
Just a little.
قليلاً فقط.
Right.
يمين.
She just mentioned it in passing.
لقد ذكرت ذلك عرضاً.
I still have to rely on acting skills.
ما زلت مضطراً للاعتماد على مهاراتي التمثيلية.
To get by.
للتغلب على الصعاب.
I also face a lot of...
أواجه أيضاً الكثير من...
Pressure from my parents.
ضغط من والديّ.
Right?
يمين؟
We're the same kind of people.
نحن من نفس النوع من الناس.
No, no, no.
لا، لا، لا.
This...
هذا...
Is also not quite the same.
الأمر ليس نفسه تماماً.
Yes.
نعم.
Not quite the same.
ليس الأمر نفسه تماماً.
This...
هذا...
You might have a slight misunderstanding.
قد يكون هناك سوء فهم بسيط.
I'm actually quite traditional.
أنا في الواقع شخص تقليدي إلى حد كبير.
But...
لكن...
But that doesn't prevent me...
لكن هذا لا يمنعني...
From accepting the world's...
من قبول ما في العالم...
Diversity.
تنوع.
Maybe we should eat first.
ربما ينبغي أن نأكل أولاً.
I'm getting a little hungry.
أشعر بالجوع قليلاً.
Yes, yes, yes.
نعم، نعم، نعم.
Let's eat.
هيا نأكل.
The food's getting cold.
بدأ الطعام يبرد.
Quick.
سريع.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Eat, eat.
كُل، كُل.
Such a harmonious relationship between three people...
علاقة متناغمة كهذه بين ثلاثة أشخاص...
This is the first time I've seen it.
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي أراه فيها.
They're actually getting along peacefully.
إنهم في الواقع يعيشون بسلام.
That's a bit strange.
هذا غريب بعض الشيء.
Should I...
هل ينبغي عليّ...
Arrange something?
هل تريد ترتيب شيء ما؟
You.
أنت.
Go notify Ou Lu.
قم بالإخطار أو القراءة.
Tell him to come see me.
قل له أن يأتي لرؤيتي.
Yes.
نعم.
I'm very happy tonight.
أنا سعيد جداً هذه الليلة.
To have dinner with you two, my family.
أتمنى أن أتناول العشاء معكما يا عائلتي.
Family.
عائلة.
One family.
عائلة واحدة.
A Wen.
أ. وين.
Let bygones be bygones.
عفا الله عما سلف.
With Xin Tong by your side...
مع وجود شين تونغ بجانبك...
I believe you'll soon find...
أعتقد أنك ستجد قريباً...
Your former happiness.
سعادتك السابقة.
I'd be lucky if she doesn't cause trouble for me.
سأكون محظوظاً إن لم تسبب لي مشاكل.
Xin Tong.
شين تونغ.
Will we still have a chance to meet up?
هل ستتاح لنا فرصة اللقاء؟
Of course, Senior.
بالتأكيد يا سيدي.
Let's meet anytime.
لنلتقي في أي وقت.
I hope you soon find...
أتمنى أن تجد قريباً...
Someone more worthy.
شخص أكثر جدارة.
Bye.
الوداع.
Your senior...
كبيرك في السن...
Really is a strange person.
إنه شخص غريب حقاً.
Check, please, you two.
الحساب من فضلكما.
How much is it?
كم سعره؟
Eighteen thousand.
ثمانية عشر ألفاً.
How...
كيف...
...much?
...كثيراً؟
Eighteen thousand.
ثمانية عشر ألفاً.
We...
نحن...
...only ordered two vegetable dishes.
...طلبت طبقين من الخضار فقط.
Spanish peas.
بازلاء إسبانية.
German white asparagus.
الهليون الأبيض الألماني.
Japanese matsutake mushrooms.
فطر ماتسوتاكي الياباني.
French potatoes.
بطاطس فرنسية.
Let me reiterate.
دعني أكرر.
During our cooperation period,
خلال فترة تعاوننا،
you are not allowed to take on similar side jobs.
لا يُسمح لك بالقيام بأعمال جانبية مماثلة.
My plan
خطتي
could be ruined.
قد يفسد.
The contract
العقد
only says I can't date.
يقول فقط إنني لا أستطيع المواعدة.
But with the little money you're paying,
لكن بالمبلغ الزهيد الذي تدفعه،
it's not enough to buy all my time.
لا يكفي ذلك لشراء كل وقتي.
Do you love money that much?
هل تحب المال إلى هذه الدرجة؟
Wrong.
خطأ.
I don't love money.
أنا لا أحب المال.
Money gives me a sense of security.
المال يمنحني شعوراً بالأمان.
To achieve
لتحقيق
my Grand Retirement-at-Thirty-Six Plan sooner,
خطتي الكبرى للتقاعد في سن السادسة والثلاثين عاجلاً،
I plan
أخطط
to trade ten years of hard labor
لاستبدال عشر سنوات من العمل الشاق
for a lifetime of enjoying the world.
للاستمتاع بالعالم مدى الحياة.
Why thirty-six?
لماذا ستة وثلاثون؟
Because in the internet industry,
لأن في صناعة الإنترنت،
thirty-five is the legal retirement age.
سن التقاعد القانوني هو خمسة وثلاثون عاماً.
Which country's law are you talking about?
عن أي قانون دولة تتحدث؟
Algorithm.
خوارزمية.
So lame.
سخيف جداً.
I hope you won't, for money
أتمنى ألا تفعل ذلك، من أجل المال
and a strange goal, have no bottom line in cooperation.
وهدف غريب، ليس له حدود دنيا في التعاون.
Then I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
أخشى أنك ستصاب بخيبة أمل.
Someone like me...
شخص مثلي...
...for money,
...من أجل المال،
has a very low bottom line.
لديها هامش ربح منخفض للغاية.
How low?
إلى أي مدى منخفض؟
Paper-thin.
رقيق كالورق.
You're blocking the rearview mirror.
أنت تحجب الرؤية في مرآة الرؤية الخلفية.
All arrangements for today
جميع الترتيبات لليوم
are
نكون
at the cafe.
في المقهى.
Right.
يمين.
I thought you've been too tired lately,
ظننت أنك متعب للغاية في الآونة الأخيرة،
so today,
إذن اليوم،
I gathered all the clients
جمعت جميع العملاء
and scheduled them together
وجدولوا مواعيدهم معًا
to improve efficiency.
لتحسين الكفاءة.
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
You're teachable.
أنت قابل للتعلم.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Ou Lu,
أنت لو،
what do you think of Wen Pei'an's girlfriend?
ما رأيك في حبيبة وين بي آن؟
How is she?
كيف حالها؟
She's...
إنها...
...quite good.
...جيد جداً.
No.
لا.
I think this girl
أعتقد أن هذه الفتاة
is too playful.
مرح للغاية.
I hope
آمل
to have Wen Pei'an
أن يكون لدى وين بي آن
meet some other girls.
قابل بعض الفتيات الأخريات.
Chairman, if there's anything you need me to do,
سيدي الرئيس، إذا كان هناك أي شيء تحتاجون مني القيام به،
just give the order.
أعطِ الأمر فقط.
You won't betray me, will you?
لن تخونني، أليس كذلك؟
Absolutely not.
بالتأكيد لا.
Facing the Chairman, one cannot be disloyal.
لا يمكن للمرء أن يكون غير مخلص أمام الرئيس.
Facing a brother, one cannot be dishonorable.
لا يجوز للمرء أن يكون غير شريف أمام أخيه.
Since ancient times, loyalty and righteousness are hard to balance.
منذ العصور القديمة، يصعب تحقيق التوازن بين الولاء والاستقامة.
So I can only arrange blind dates under the guise of business.
لذا لا يمكنني ترتيب مواعيد غرامية عمياء إلا تحت ستار العمل.
Dad.
أب.
We are truly in love.
نحن مغرمان ببعضنا حقاً.
Why don't you believe it?
لماذا لا تصدق ذلك؟
It's your eyes
إنها عيناك
that gave you away.
هذا كشف أمرك.
In your eyes,
في عينيك،
I don't see
لا أرى
the love that endures
الحب الذي يدوم
through thick and thin.
في السراء والضراء.
Dad,
أب،
you and mother have been
لقد كنت أنت وأمي
a marriage in name only for twenty years.
زواج صوري فقط لمدة عشرين عاماً.
You simply don't understand what love is.
أنت ببساطة لا تفهم ما هو الحب.
Now,
الآن،
you're forcing me into a marriage alliance with someone else,
أنت تجبرني على الزواج من شخص آخر،
to repeat your life.
لتكرار حياتك.
I won't accept it.
لن أقبل بذلك.
If you don't listen to me,
إذا لم تستمع إليّ،
starting now,
ابتداءً من الآن،
I'll confiscate all your assets
سأصادر جميع ممتلكاتك
and sever
وفصل
our father-son relationship.
علاقتنا بين الأب والابن.
Starting tomorrow,
ابتداءً من الغد،
I will become an orphan.
سأصبح يتيماً.
I'll chop wood,
سأقوم بتقطيع الحطب،
feed the horses.
أطعم الخيول.
We'll travel the world together.
سنسافر حول العالم معًا.
From then on, we'll care about grain and vegetable prices.
من الآن فصاعدًا، سنهتم بأسعار الحبوب والخضراوات.
We might not afford a house,
قد لا نتمكن من شراء منزل،
but we can face the sea,
لكن بإمكاننا مواجهة البحر،
with spring warmth
مع دفء الربيع
and roses blooming.
والورود تتفتح.
Thank you, Uncle, for raising me.
شكراً لك يا عمي على تربيتي.
Thank you, Uncle.
شكراً لك يا عمي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Ungrateful son!
يا ابني الجاحد!